Guide to the Institute for the Future Reports M1186
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Accession 2017-188 (Boxes 13-48)
  - World Grain Trade in the Next Decade/ G. Schmid, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Pitfalls in the Social Evaluation of Teleconferencing Media/ R. Johansen, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - "FORUM/ R. Amara J. Vallee", 1974 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Interdependence Has Its Limits/ G. Schmid, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - The FORUM Project/ J. Vallee, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - "Pragmatics and Dynamics of Computer Conferencing/ J. Vallee R. Johansen H. Lipinski T. Wilson", 1976 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Education for Survival/ R. Amara, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - "Computer Conferencing/ R. Johansen J. Vallee M. Palmer", 1976 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - "Computer Networks and the Interactive Use of Geologic Data/ J. Vallee T. Wilson", 1975 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - "Impact of a Computer-Based Communications Network on the Working Patterns of Researchers/ R. Johansen J. Vallee", 1976 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - "Distributed Management of Scientific Projects/ J. Vallee B. Gibbs", 1976 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - "Planning with Scenarios/ M. Palmer G. Schmid", 1976 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - "Remote Viewing Experiments through Computer Conferencing/ J. Vallee A. Hastings G. Askevold", 1976 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Some Observations on the Interaction of Technology and Society Amara, Roy, 1975-12-01 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Social and Technological Forecasting in the Soviet Union Randolph, Robert H., 1976-12-01 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Modeling as a Communication Process Vallee, Jacques, 1977-03-01 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Futurology Applied to Education Johansen, Robert Samuel, Patricia A., 1943-, 1977-04-01 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - There Ain’t No User Science Vallee, Jacques, 1977-07-01 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Learning the Limits of Teleconferencing Johansen, Robert Vallee, Jacques Collins, Kent, 1977-09-01 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Probing the Future Amara, Roy, 1976-07-01 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Looking Ahead at the Third Century Amara, Roy, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Linking the Corporation to the Future Amara, Roy Lipinski, Andrew J., 1977-04-01 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Planning, Futures, and the Skeptics Amara, Roy, 1978-01-01 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Five Emergent Features of U.S. Society and Their Impact on Management in the Next Decade Amara, Roy, 1975-12-01 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - America’s Continuing Revolution—The Dispersion of Power Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1978-03-01 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Strategic Planning in a Changing Corporate Environment Amara, Roy, 1979-03-01 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Social Evaluations of Teleconferencing Johansen, Robert, 1977-12-01 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Communicating the Future Lipinski, Andrew J., 1978-04-01 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Interpersonal Communication through Computers Johansen, Robert, 1978-05-01 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Electronic Meetings Johansen, Robert Vallee, Jacques Spangler, Kathleen, 1978-10-01 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Communication Needs in Computer Modeling Lipinski, Hubert M. Amara, Roy Spangler, Kathleen, 1978-12-01 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Identifying the Information Space of a Model Lipinski, Hubert M. Spangler, Kathleen Traweek, Sharon, 1978-10-01 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Future of Voluntarism Amara, Roy, 1978-11-01 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Cross-Impact Analysis—Extended KSIM Lipinski, Hubert M. Tydeman, John, 1978-12-01 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Interactive Monitoring of Computer-Based Group Communication Spangler, Kathleen Lipinski, Hubert M. Plummer, Robert P., 1978-12-01 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - The U.S. in the Decade Ahead Amara, Roy, 1978-12-01 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Home Information Systems Nyhan, Michael J. Johansen, Robert Plummer, Robert P., 1979-05-01 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Beyond Protectionism Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1979-07-01 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - International Security and the World Economy Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1979-09-01 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - 4004 Futures for Teletext and Videotex in the U.S. Plummer, Robert P. Johansen, Robert Nyhan, Michael J. Holmlöv, Per Gunnar, 1951-, 1979-07-01 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Computer-Based Teleconferencing Johansen, Robert DeGrasse, Robert, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - An Interactive Computer-Based Approach to Aid Group Problem Formulation Tydeman, John Lipinski, Hubert M. Spang, Sara, 1980-01-01 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Two-Year Colleges in the 1980s Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Russell, Lawrence, 1980-02-01 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - The Future of Management Amara, Roy, 1980-02-01 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Videotex and Teletext in the U.S. Nyhan, Michael J. Johansen, Robert Plummer, Robert P., 1980-02-01 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - The Common Sense of Trying Out Videotex Johansen, Robert, 1980-02-01 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Supporting Task-Focused Communication Lipinski, Hubert M. Spang, Sara Tydeman, John, 1980-06-01 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Graphic Communication in a Group Setting Lipinski, Hubert M. Spang, Sara Tydeman, John, 1980-06-01 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Videotex Tydeman, John Johansen, Robert Lipinski, Hubert M. Nyhan, Michael J., 1980-06-01 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Communication in Interactive Simulation Lipinski, Hubert M. Spang, Sara, 1980-07-01 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Imperatives for Tomorrow Amara, Roy, 1980-07-01 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Establishing a Telephone Conferencing System Connell, Eileen, 1980-08-01 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Teletext and Videotex in North America Johansen, Robert Nyhan, Michael J. Plummer, Robert P., 1980-03-01 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Laboratory Costs and Utilization—A Framework for Analysis and Policy Design Hardwick, David Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Tydeman, John Cassidy, Paul Chase, William, 1980-11-01 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Analyzing the Factors Contributing to Rising Laboratory Costs Hardwick, David Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Tydeman, John Cassidy, Paul Chase, William, 1980-11-01 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Structuring Complexity of Testing—A Process Control Approach to Limiting Unnecessary Laboratory Use Hardwick, David Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Tydeman, John Cassidy, Paul Chase, William, 1980-11-01 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Yellow Pages at the Forefront of U.S. Videotex Policy Debate Adler, Richard, 1942- Nyhan, Michael J. Tydeman, John, 1981-08-01 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - A Framework for Corporate Strategic Planning Amara, Roy, 1980-09-01 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The Videotex Invention Nyhan, Michael J., 1980-02-01 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Planning for Arizona’s Future Amara, Roy, 1980-10-01 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Health Care in Australia 1980-2000 Tydeman, John Mitchell, Robert, 1979-06-01 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Cost of Procedures Quality Control in the Clinical Laboratory Tydeman, John Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Hardwick, David Cassidy, Paul, 1980-09-01 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - The Cost of Laboratory Technology Tydeman, John Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Kasap, Draginja Poulin, Mary, 1981-05-01 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - You Can See the Results, But What Went into the Making? Burns, Red, 1981-07-01 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Can Health Care (as we know it) Survive in the Eighties? Tydeman, John, 1980-02-01 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Toward the Year 2000 Amara, Roy, 1981-01-01 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - National League of Cities/OPRE, Teleconference on Human Services Planning, A Report of Participant Reactions Nyhan, Michael J., 1981-01-01 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Videotex in the United States—Toward Information Diversity Tydeman, John, 1981-05-01 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - The Effects of Current Economic Pressures on the Scope for New Telecommunications Services in the Field of Developmental Disabilities Elton, M. C. J., 1981-07-01 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - National Networking Todd, Seldon P.‏, 1981-07-01 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Building A New Partnership Burns, Red Quarles, Pat, 1981-07-01 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Key Issues for the Print Industry in the '80s Amara, Roy, 1981-10-01 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Productivity Failure? Reindustrialization? Careful! Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1981-01-01 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - HUB Adler, Richard, 1942- Lipinski, Hubert M., 1982-01-01 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - The New Activism and the Corporation Amara, Roy Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1981-10-01 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Choosing an Electronic Message System, 1980-09-01 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - 1981 Audio Conferencing Handbook Rowan, Paul D., 1981-02-01 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - User Perspectives Chupack, Stephan F. Sbardellati, Edward Thomas, Karen Viets, Lee Wickes, Gail, 1981-07-01 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Report Adler, Richard, 1942- Nyhan, Michael J. Tydeman, John, 1981-04-01 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Teletext and Videotex Tydeman, John, 1981-08-01 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - The Chip at Work Zwimpfer, Lawrence, 1981-08-01 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Teletext and Videotex Standards for the U.S. Lipinski, Hubert M. Tydeman, John Zwimpfer, Lawrence, 1981-06-01 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Growth in Teleconferencing Johansen, Robert Hansell, Kathleen Jane Green, David, 1981-12-01 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Approaches to Teleconferencing Justification Charles, Jeff, 1981-12-01 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Videotex Tydeman, John, 1982-02-01 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Teletext and Videotex Tydeman, John, 1982-06-01 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - The Competitors to Cable Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1982-10-01 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - The Consumer and Business Markets for Videotex in the U.S. Tydeman, John Adler, Richard, 1942- Lipinski, Hubert M., 1982-06-01 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Center Stage for Human Resources Amara, Roy, 1983-02-01 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Uncertainty Lipinski, Andrew J., 1983-03-01 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Communicating Probabilistic Forecasts Lipinski, Andrew J. Lipinski, Hubert M., 1983-05-01 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - U.S. Management’s Reaction to Uncertainty Lipinski, Andrew J., 1984-05-01 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Issues of the Future Lipinski, Andrew J., 1984-10 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - From the Analyst to the Executive Lipinski, Andrew J., 1984-11-01 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Teleconferencing Success Stories Johansen, Robert, 1985-03-01 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Twelve Emerging Technologies for the 1990s Amara, Roy, 1985-12-01 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Lawyers in the 1990s Saffo, Paul, 1985-12-01 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - What to Expect from Teleconferencing Johansen, Robert Bullen, Christine V., 1984-08-01 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The Maturing of Corporate Planning Amara, Roy, 1986-10-01 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - The Impact of New Diagnostic Technologies on Health Care Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Poulin, Mary McNeal, Barbara, 1985-07-01 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - User Needs Workshops Johansen, Robert Baker, Ellen, 1983-06-01 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Business Television for Competitive Advantage Charles, Jeff, 1986-12-01 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Looking Ahead at American Health Care Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Amara, Roy Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1987-02-01 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - From Reflection to Action Hassam, Amin Priest, Norm Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1987-04-01 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - What the Baby Boomers Can Expect From Private Employee Health Care Systems Amara, Roy, 1987-04-01 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Seniornet Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1987-12-01 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - The Chemical Industry in the 1990s Cook, A., 1988-07-01 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - What We Have Learned about Forecasting and Planning Amara, Roy, 1988-02-01 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Groupware Johansen, Robert Bullen, Christine V., 1988-05-01 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Telecommunications, Information Technology, and Rural Development Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1988-07-01 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Technology for Electronic Publishing and Computer Software Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1988-01-01 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Columns by Paul Saffo, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Scope and Contents
    “The Death of a Design,” 1987 “Invasion of the Laser Crud,” Personal Computing, May 1987, pp. 57,60 “The Paper Revolution,” Personal Computing, July 1987, pp. 43+ “What’s Beyond Paper?”, Personal Comput­ing, December 1988, pp. 69-70+ “Surfing for Information,” Personal Comput­ing, July 1989, pp. 213,214 “Fax, PC Collision Will Be a Boon for the Office of the Future,” Personal Computing, April 15, 1991, p. 51 “Cheap Laser Technology Will Turn 1980s Dreams into 1990s Realities, Personal Computing, June 1992 “The Electronic Future is Upon Us,” New York Times, “Forum,” June 1992
  - Believable Broadband for Business, Four Scenarios Saffo, Paul Johansen, Robert, 1988-10-01 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Looking to the 1990s Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1989-06-01 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - New Directions on Innovation Amara, Roy, 1989-03-01 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Health Care Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Amara, Roy, 1989-04-01 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Business Teams Johansen, Robert, 1989-06-01 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Groupware and Collaborative Systems, A Big Picture View Johansen, Robert, 1989-08-01 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Perspectives on San Mateo County in the Year 2000 Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1989-09-01 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Outlook for San Mateo County Youth in the Year 2000 Saveri, Andrea, 1989-09-01 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - International Outlook for the Decade of the 1990s Amara, Roy, 1989-10-01 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Groupware Johansen, Robert, 1989-11-01 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - At Work in the U.S. in the 1990s Amara, Roy, 1990-02-01 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Health Care in the 1990s Amara, Roy, 1990-10-01 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Teams for Tomorrow Johansen, Robert, 1990-10-01 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Health Care Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1991-01-01 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Future of the American Family Donzelli, Jill, 1991-10-01 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Is the Pharmaceutical Industry on the Right Track? Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1990-10-01 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Five Scenarios Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1991-07-01 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Impact of Telecommunications on Urban Development Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Saveri, Andrea, 1991-11-01 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Outlook for the California Economy Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1992-01-01 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - The Future and the American Health Care System Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1991-11-01 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Introduction to Evaluation of Teleconferencing —A Beginner’s Guide Charles, Jeff, 1990-08-01 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Adaptations of Distance Education in the 1990s Charles, Jeff, 1992-08-01 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Evaluation of the North Slope Borough Teleconference Network Charles, Jeff Ozawa, Nancy, 1992-08-01 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Outlook for Mexico and the United States in the 1990s—A Conference Sponsored by AMROP International, Mexico City, June 1992 Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1993-05-01 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Does California Have an Economic Future? Presented to the California Business-Higher Education Forum Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1994-04-01 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - The Intersection of Biotechnology and Information Technology, 1999-06-01 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - A Study of Potential Changes in Employee Benefits, Volume I Gordon, Theodore J., 1969-04-01 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - A Study of Potential Changes in Employee Benefits, Volume II Gordon, Theodore J., 1969-04-01 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - A Study of Potential Changes in Employee Benefits, Volume III Gordon, Theodore J., 1969-04-01 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - A Study of Potential Changes in Employee Benefits, Volume IV Gordon, Theodore J., 1969-04-01 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Development of Long-Range Forecasting Methods for Connecticut Helmer-Hirschberg, Olaf Gordon, Theodore J. Enzer, Selwyn De Brigard, Raul‏ Rochberg, Richard, 1969-09-01 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Forecasts of Some Technological and Scientific Developments and Their Societal Consequences (EPRC, CRC, WU) Gordon, Theodore J. Ament, Robert H., 1969-09-01 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Some Potential Societal Developments De Brigard, Raul‏ Helmer-Hirschberg, Olaf, 1970-04-01 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Issues and Opportunities in the State of Connecticut Enzer, Selwyn De Brigard, Raul‏, 1970-03-01 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - A Simulation Game for the Study of State Policies (CRC) Enzer, Selwyn Gordon, Theodore J. Rochberg, Richard Buchele, Robert, 1969-09-01 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - The Use of Cross-Impact Matrices for Forecasting and Planning (EPRC, CRC, WU) Rochberg, Richard Gordon, Theodore J. Helmer-Hirschberg, Olaf, 1970-04-01 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Research on Cross-Impact Techniques with Applications to Selected Problems in Economics, Political Science, and Technology Assessment (NSF) Gordon, Theodore J. Rochberg, Richard Enzer, Selwyn, 1970-08-01 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Some Prospects for Residential Housing by 1985 (OCF) Enzer, Selwyn, 1971-01-01 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Report on the Future of the Future-State-of-the-Union Reports (Russell Sage) Helmer-Hirschberg, Olaf, 1970-10-01 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The Future of Newsprint, 1970-2000, A Special Industry Report (MB) Baran, Paul, 1971-12-01 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Some Developments in Plastics and Competing Materials by 1985 (OCF) Enzer, Selwyn, 1971-01-01 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - A Framework for Community Development Action Planning, Volume I Becker, Harold S. De Brigard, Raul‏, 1971-02-01 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - A Framework for Community Development Action Planning, Volume II Becker, Harold S. De Brigard, Raul‏, 1971-02-01 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - The Future of the Telephone Industry, 1970-1985, A Special Industry Report (AT&T) Baran, Paul Lipinski, Andrew J., 1971-09-01 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - A Forecast of the Interaction Between Business and Society in the Next Five Years (Chase Manhattan) Gordon, Theodore J. Little, Dennis L. Strudler, Harold L. Lustgarten, Donna D., 1971-04-01 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Futures Research as an Aid to Government Planning in Canada Enzer, Selwyn Boucher, Wayne I. Lazar, Fred, 1946-, 1971-08-01 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Futures Research as an Aid to Government Planning in Canada Enzer, Selwyn Boucher, Wayne I. Lazar, Fred, 1946-, 1971-08-01 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - On the Nature of Economic Losses Arising from Computer-Based Systems in the Next 15 Years (Skandia) Salancik, Gerald R. Gordon, Theodore J. Adams, Neale, 1972-03-01 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Federal/State Science Policy and Connecticut Enzer, Selwyn, 1971-10-01 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Some Prospects for Social Change by 1985 and Their Impact on Time/Money Budgets (GTE) Enzer, Selwyn Little, Dennis L. Lazar, Fred, 1946-, 1972-03-01 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Potential Market Demand for Two-Way Information Services to the Home, 1970-1990 (DOC) Baran, Paul, 1971-12-01 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - One the Future State of the Union (Russell Sage) Helmer-Hirschberg, Olaf, 1972-05-01 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Some Considerations Concerning Bankruptcy Reform (NSF) Enzer, Selwyn De Brigard, Raul‏ Lazar, Fred, 1946-, 1973-03-01 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Toward Understanding the Social Impact of Computers (NSF) Amara, Roy, 1974-05-01 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Some Impacts of No-Fault Automobile Insurance—A Technology Assessment, Volume I (NSF) Enzer, Selwyn, 1974-03-01 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Some Impacts of No-Fault Automobile Insurance—A Technology Assessment, Volume II (NSF) Enzer, Selwyn, 1974-05-01 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Group Communication through Computers, Volume 1 Vallee, Jacques Lipinski, Hubert M. Miller, Richard, 1974-07-01 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Group Communication through Computers, volume 3 Vallee, Jacques Johansen, Robert Lipinski, Hubert M. Spangler, Kathleen Wilson, Thaddeus, 1975-10-01 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "Priorities in Postsecondary Education (The Arthur Vining Davis Foundations) Formerly SR-64" Palmer, Michael Chula, Margaret Jensen, Carreen Johansen, Robert Samuel, Patricia A., 1943-, 1977-02-01 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Electronic Meetings Johansen, Robert Vallee, Jacques Spangler, Kathleen Shirts, R. Garry (Robert Garry), 1934-, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Future Societal Developments and Postsecondary Education (Lilly Endowment, Inc.) Formerly SR-72" Johansen, Robert Samuel, Patricia A., 1943-, 1977-03-01 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Alternative Futures and Postsecondary Education in Pennsylvania (Buhl Foundation and PACU) Formerly SR-82 Johansen, Robert McNulty, Maureen, 1977-07-01 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Group Communication through Computers, Volume 4 Vallee, Jacques Johansen, Robert Lipinski, Hubert M. Spangler, Kathleen Wilson, Thaddeus, 1978-01-01 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Group Communication through Computers, Volume 5 Johansen, Robert DeGrasse, Robert Wilson, Thaddeus, 1978-02-01 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Education Johansen, Robert McNulty, Maureen McNeal, Barbara, 1978-08-01 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Sophisticated Protectionism Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Phillips, Owen, 1978-11-01 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Interactive Group Modeling Vian, Kathleen Lipinski, Hubert M. Plummer, Robert P., 1979-08-01 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Interactive Group Modeling Vian, Kathleen Lipinski, Hubert M. Plummer, Robert P. Spang, Sara, 1979-08-01 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Interactive Group Modeling Vian, Kathleen Lipinski, Hubert M. Spang, Sara Tydeman, John, 1979-08-01 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Interactive Group Modeling Spang, Sara McNeal, Barbara Vian, Kathleen Spangler, 1979-08-01 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Policy Choices in Vocational Education Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1979-12-01 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Policy Choices in Vocational Education Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1979-12-01 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Electronic Mail Among University Training Centers McNeal, Barbara, 1980-11-01 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications and Developmentally Disabled People Johansen, Robert McNeal, Barbara Nyhan, Michael J., 1981-08-01 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The HUB Project—Computer-Based Support for Group Problem Solving Lipinski, Hubert M. Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1982-01-01 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - A Survey of Permanently Installed Teleconferencing Rooms in North America (AT&T) Formerly SR-100 Johansen, Robert, 1981-10-01 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Information Technology Environment for Medical Colleges Over the Next Decade (AAMC) Tydeman, John, 1982-06-01 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - A Snapshot View of Communication Patterns (New Hampshire Division of Vocational Rehabilitation) Formerly SR-121 Nyhan, Michael J. Charles, Jeff Vian, Kathleen, 1982-07-01 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The "Market for Teletext in the United States (Revised SR-142, 10/82)" Adler, Richard, 1942- Lipinski, Hubert M., 1983-02-01 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Health Care Services Environment Poulin, Mary Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1983-06 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Estimates for Alternatives to Pacific Bell Services (See SR-216), 1984-07-01 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - The Impact of New Diagnostic Technologies on the Practice of Medicine, 1982, 95 (See R-60A), 1985-01-01 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Impact of New Diagnostic Technologies on the Practice of Medicine, 1982, 95 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - New Strategies for Innovations in Medical Information Systems (John Hartford) Poulin, Mary, 1984-12-01 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Robot Outlook (CDC) Amara, Roy Mittman, Robert, 1985-02-01 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Long-Term Environmental Trends for ITV (Cresap, McCormick & Paget) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1985-05-01 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Computer Industry Outlook, Draft (CDC) Mittman, Robert, 1985-08-01 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Computer Industry Outlook, Final Report and Appendix (CDC) Mittman, Robert, 1985-12-01 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Drug and Pharmaceuticals Industry (CDC) Mittman, Robert Poulin, Mary, 1985-08-01 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The "Apparel Industry—The Other California Final Report and Appendix (CDC)" Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1985-08 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Software Information Processing (CDC) Saffo, Paul Mittman, Robert, 1985-08-01 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "Software Information Processing (CDC) Revised" Saffo, Paul Mittman, Robert, 1986-02-01 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - The Telecommunications Industry Mittman, Robert Goldberg, JoAnne, 1985-09-01 (Box 22, Folder 14)